In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to pronounce the AI as in BAI diphthong.
我们将学习如何发音 AI，如在 BAI 双元音中。
Diphthongs are a combination of two sounds,
双元音是两个声音的组合，
so they have a starting position and an ending position.
因此它们有一个起始位置和一个结束位置。
In the first position,
在第一个位置，
the jaw is more dropped than in the second position.
下巴比第二个位置更下垂。
The back of the tongue stretches up a little bit.
舌头的后部稍微向上伸展。
As the mouth moves into the second position,
当嘴巴移动到第二个位置时，
the jaw drops less as the front part of the tongue arches up towards the roof of the mouth.
下巴下垂得更少，而舌头的前部向上拱向口腔的顶部。
For both the beginning and the end of this diphthong,
在这个双元音的开始和结束时，
the tongue tip touches the back of the bottom front teeth.
舌尖触碰下前牙的后面。
Let's watch up close and in slow motion,
让我们近距离慢动作观看，
where you can really see the front part of the tongue arching up.
你可以真正看到舌头的前部拱起。
The jaw drops and the front part of the tongue stays down,
下巴下垂，舌头的前部保持向下，
with the tip touching the back of the bottom front teeth.
舌尖触碰下前牙的后面。
Immediately,
立即，
the tongue moves into the second position,
舌头移动到第二个位置，
the top front arching up towards the roof of the mouth.
舌头的前部向上拱向口腔的顶部。
As the tongue arches up,
当舌头拱起时，
there's less jaw drop.
下巴下垂得更少。
Here's the word high.
这是单词 high。
Jaw drops with the front of the tongue down,
下巴下垂，舌头的前部向下，
then the jaw lifts as the front of the tongue arches towards the roof of the mouth.
然后下巴抬起，舌头的前部拱向口腔的顶部。
In a stressed syllable,
在重读音节中，
the AI diphthong curves up, then down.
AI 双元音先上升，然后下降。
High,
High，
AI.
AI。
In an unstressed syllable, it's lower and flatter in pitch,
在非重读音节中，音调更低更平，
as well as quicker and quieter.
而且更快更安静。
AI, AI.
AI，AI。
The diphthong is unstressed in the word idea,
在单词 idea 中，双元音是非重读的，
AI.
AI。
Let's take a look at this word.
让我们看看这个单词。
The jaw drops, but just a little bit less than it would in a stressed syllable.
下巴下垂，但比重读音节时稍微少一点。
Then the tongue arches up towards the roof of the mouth before the tip goes to the roof of the mouth for the D.
然后舌头拱起向口腔的顶部，然后舌尖到达口腔顶部发 D 音。
The AI diphthong stressed.
AI 双元音重读。
High.
High。
AI.
AI。
The AI diphthong unstressed.
AI 双元音非重读。
Idea.
Idea。
AI.
AI。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Exercise.
Exercise。
I.
I。
Exercise.
Exercise。
Wine.
Wine。
I.
I。
Wine.
Wine。
Bright.
Bright。
I.
I。
Bright.
Bright。
Guy.
Guy。
I.
I。
Guy.
Guy。
Allies.
Allies。
I.
I。
Allies.
Allies。
Sky.
Sky。
I.
I。
Sky.
Sky。